

Mateusz Cedro

DATA SCIENTIST & MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I'm a data scientist who delivers Machine Learning & Artificial Intelligence solutions for data-driven projects in business and research. Especially interested in explaining complex ML/AI models and data visualisation. Check out my recent projects at GitHub.

KNOWLEDGE & SKILLS

Machine Learning & Deep Learning Modeling

Neural Networks (Deep, Convolutional, Recurrent)

Computer Vision (Classification, Segmentation)

Explaninable Artificial Intelligence XAI (SHAP, LIME)

Advanced Data Vizualization

Econometric Modelling

Text Mining

Algorithmics (Algorithms for Data Science)

Data Analysis & Data Manipulation

Statistics, Probability Calculus & Linear Algebra

Critical & Analytical Thinking

Marketing & Consumer Behaviour

TECHNOLOGIES

Python (PyTorch, Scikit-learn, Numpy, TensorFlow, Pandas, Seaborn, Matplotlib, Shap, Lime, Quantus) SQL

Big Data (BigQuery)

Cloud Computing (Azure, Google Cloud Platform)
PowerBI, Power Query

SOFT SKILLS

Group Cooperation & Leadership

Public Speeches, Communication & Presentations

LANGUAGES

English C1 (IELTS Certificate), German B1

Polish (Native)

CONTACT

Phone number: +48 606 394 173

E-mail address: mateusz.cedro7@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mateusz-cedro GitHub: https://github.com/mateuszcedro/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deep Learning Engineer at Data Juice Lab (Jul 2022 - Dec 2022)

Artificial Intelligence in Medicine

- Developing State-Of-The-Art Deep Learning Computer Vision models for medical disease classification and segmentation in Python (Convolutional Neural Networks, PyTorch)
- Medical X-ray images analysis & preprocessing
- · Working in Azure cloud service

Data Scientist (Analyst) at Health Labs Care (Feb 2022 - Jul 2022) eCommerce

- Delivering solutions via Machine Learning and Econometric modeling methods
- · Deep data analysis
- Business insights delivering
- SQL & ETL
- Data visualisation for data and non-data departments
- PowerBI
- · Colaboration with stakeholders
- Process optimization
- Forecasts performing
- A/B testing

EDUCATION

MSc in Data Science & Business Analytics

(2021 - 2023) University of Warsaw

Master's thesis: Explanation of self-developed deep learning computer vision models builted on COVID-19 lung X-ray images

Erasmus Exchange in Bologna, Italy

(Feb 2023 - Jun 2023) University of Bologna Computer Science and Engineering Department

BSc in Economics, BSc in Management

Double Degree Programme

(2018 - 2021) University of Warsaw

Erasmus Exchange in Antwerp, Belgium

(Sep 2020 - Jun 2021) University of Antwerp

VOLUNTARY ORGANISATIONS

NZS Independent Students' Association

High School Council Member

ZHR Scouting Organisation Leader Assistant 2016-2018